(Leonard:)All right, Sheldon, to start our quest...
...you need to open this Christmas gift
I got you.
(Sheldon:)A Christmas gift?
(Sheldon:)You know I don't enjoy Christmas.
- What's wrong with Christmas?
- Oh, where to begin?
(Sheldon:)Trees indoors.
Overuse of the words "'tis" and "'twas."
(Sheldon:)And the absurd custom of one stocking.
(Sheldon:)Everyone knows socks belong in pairs.
(Sheldon:)- Who uses one sock?
- A pirate with a peg leg. Heh.
(Sheldon:)Actually, that helps. Thank you.
(Leonard:)Would you just look inside?
Oh, a scroll! I like scrolls.
They're my third-favorite system
of transmitting the written word.
(Sheldon:)After stone tablets and skywriting.
"You have all been summoned to join
a thrilling Dungeons & Dragons adventure.
(Sheldon:)Your quest begins in a secret
northern village of elves...
...who have all been massacred."